Why do we need to actually hold meetings.
为什么我们需要实际举行会议。
Well there can be a huge number of reasons to hold hold a meeting and whether it's a group of people
开会的原因有很多，无论是一群人
or just two one of those might be in negotiation.
或者其中只有两个可能正在谈判中。
We've talked about that but maybe for example two groups from two different companies might get together
我们已经讨论过这一点，但也许例如来自两家不同公司的两个小组可能会聚在一起
to negotiate some very large deal for example and they might discuss terms they might try to compromise
例如，谈判一些非常大的交易，他们可能会讨论他们可能试图妥协的条款
or they might decide that they can't come to an agreement and then they at least know why.
或者他们可能决定无法达成协议，然后他们至少知道原因。
Because they had the meeting.
因为他们开会了。
Maybe it's a brainstorming meeting.
也许这是一次头脑风暴会议。
These are in my opinion the most fun.
这些在我看来是最有趣的。
Brainstorming is when everybody is giving ideas often to solve a problem or to come up with something
头脑风暴是当每个人经常提出想法来解决问题或想出一些东西时
new that people haven't thought of before.
人们以前没有想到的新事物。
Maybe in a company for example.
例如，也许在一家公司。
So let's say there's a problem with one product in this company and that's what they sell.
因此，假设这家公司的一种产品存在问题，而这就是他们销售的产品。
One of the things they sell and it's not working it's not they're not selling a lot of that.
他们卖的东西之一，它不起作用，不是他们没有卖很多东西。
They're trying to figure out why.
他们正试图找出原因。
So they get everybody together.
所以他们让大家聚在一起。
Maybe the people who are responsible for making strategic decisions strategic is the adjective strategy
也许负责制定战略决策的人是战略形容词
means planning and making decisions about what what can help the company or what can accomplish goals.
意味着计划和决定什么可以帮助公司或什么可以实现目标。
OK so basically everyone's throwing out ideas when we brainstorm.
好的，所以当我们进行头脑风暴时，基本上每个人都会提出想法。
There's a storm going on in your brain.
一场风暴正在你的大脑中进行。
We're not usually focused on coming to an agreement about which one we're going to do maybe but the
我们通常不会专注于就我们可能要做的事情达成协议，但是
general idea is you say what you think.
一般的想法是你说你的想法。
Then you say then you say and then you say and I'll write it down on the whiteboard and we'll get all
然后你说，然后你说，然后你说，我会在白板上写下来，我们会得到所有
the ideas down or on the board and then we can discuss them and decide which one is best.
将想法写下来或放在板上，然后我们可以讨论它们并决定哪个是最好的。
But first let's brainstorm and it can be a lot of fun.
但首先让我们集思广益，这会很有趣。
And often if you have five or six people in a room together brainstorming that can be really really
通常，如果你有五六个人在一个房间里一起头脑风暴，那真的是真的
fun really interesting.
有趣真的很有趣。
Another reason you might have a meeting is to discuss policy changes now policies are rules within usually
您可能会开会的另一个原因是讨论政策变化，现在政策通常是其中的规则
an organization or a company and sometimes policy needs to be changed based on something that happened.
一个组织或公司，有时需要根据发生的事情改变政策。
So let's say there is a new law in the country that this company is in or the state or whatever.
因此，假设这家公司所在的国家/地区或州或其他地方有一项新法律。
And so because of that law the company then needs to make a change.
因此，由于该法律，公司需要做出改变。
Well they will have a meeting to discuss how the company's rules will change based on that change in
好吧，他们将开会讨论公司的规则将如何根据这种变化而改变
the law or perhaps there is a problem that's come up recently could be related to company culture and
法律或最近出现的问题可能与公司文化和
how employees interact with each other.
员工之间如何互动。
Or maybe it's related to payment whatever.
或者也许它与付款有关。
Maybe some changes need to happen.
也许需要发生一些改变。
These are policy changes and the management staff staff is a group of people by the way.
这些是政策变化，顺便说一句，管理人员是一群人。
It's not each person you're not a staff usually you're a staff member.
不是每个人你都不是员工，通常你是员工。
Each person is a staff member.
每个人都是工作人员。
So the management staff might get together and discuss what policies might need to change in order to
因此，管理人员可能会聚在一起讨论可能需要更改哪些政策，以便
resolve the problem or adjust or whatever needs to happen.
解决问题或调整或任何需要发生的事情。
Something needs to change in the rules of the company.
公司的规则需要改变一些东西。
So policy changes so the management staff or the sometimes senior staff may get together to decide what
因此政策发生了变化，因此管理人员或有时高级人员可能会聚在一起决定什么
policy changes to make or perhaps if they've already decided how to implement how to implement those
要进行的政策更改，或者如果他们已经决定如何实施如何实施这些
changes.
变化。
If we implement something that means we put it into place we put it into action.
如果我们实施一些意味着我们将其付诸实施的东西，我们就会将其付诸行动。
This is the plan.
这是计划。
Okay great.
好，太棒了。
We have a plan.
我们有一个计划。
Now let's talk about how we implement the plan or how we actually make it real.
现在让我们谈谈ab了解我们如何实施计划或我们如何真正实现计划。
How we actually put it into place into place put it into place.
我们如何将其实际落实到位。
Now similar to a brainstorming meeting we might have a problem problem solving meeting.
现在类似于头脑风暴会议，我们可能有一个解决问题的会议。
This could be a little bit different than brainstorming.
这可能与头脑风暴有点不同。
We know exactly what the problem is.
我们确切地知道问题是什么。
And we're trying to find solutions.
我们正在努力寻找解决方案。
Maybe there are only two options so we're not really brainstorming about what to do but we're trying
也许只有两种选择，所以我们并没有真正集思广益，但我们正在尝试
to decide maybe which option is best A or B and maybe we're weighing the pros and cons and having a
来决定哪个选项是最好的 A 或 B，也许我们正在权衡利弊并有一个
discussion about what are the pros more or the cons more we could say for example the the pros outweigh
讨论更多的优点或缺点，我们可以说例如优点大于
the cons or we could say the cons outweigh outweigh the pros.
缺点或者我们可以说缺点大于优点。
It goes either way.
无论哪种方式。
So in order to figure out whether A is better than B or B is better than a we'll get together and talk
所以为了弄清楚 A 比 B 好还是 B 比 a 好，我们会聚在一起讨论
about which one is going to be the best in the long term.
从长远来看，哪一个将是最好的。
So if we're talking about long term or short term we're talking about immediate benefits or benefits
因此，如果我们谈论的是长期或短期，我们谈论的是直接利益或利益
down the road.
在路上。
In the far future down we sometimes say down the road.
在遥远的未来，我们有时会说在路上。
Well I think that I think that a is a good choice but it really only solves the immediate problem.
好吧，我认为我认为 a 是一个不错的选择，但它实际上只能解决眼前的问题。
I think B will be better down the road.
我认为B会更好。
I think B will be better in the long term.
从长远来看，我认为B会更好。
The last one I want to mention is alignment.
我要提到的最后一个是对齐。
Now this one might just be for each department in a company each department or maybe each department
现在这个可能只是针对公司中的每个部门每个部门或每个部门
head to update everyone else about what's going on in their department.
前往向其他人通报他们部门的最新情况。
This is just to make sure that everybody is on the same page on the same page.
这只是为了确保每个人都在同一页面上的同一页面上。
We often use this expression.
我们经常使用这种表达方式。
We need to make sure we're all on the same page so that decisions I make don't negatively affect decisions
我们需要确保我们都在同一个页面上，这样我做出的决定不会对决定产生负面影响
you make so that we can all make the right decisions so that we can move in a direction altogether so
您做出这样的决定是为了我们都可以做出正确的决定，以便我们可以完全朝着一个方向前进
that we can have alignment alignment means we are in the same sort of direction all going together right.
我们可以进行对齐对齐意味着我们在同一个方向上，都在正确的方向上。
I can also say to keep someone in the loop to keep someone in the loop means that they know what's going
我也可以说让某人处于循环中以使某人保持在循环中意味着他们知道发生了什么
on.
上。
If one person is going to leave for a week and won't be able to maybe take part in any of the meetings
如果一个人要离开一周并且可能无法参加任何会议
he might say to his or she might say to her colleague please keep me in the loop.
他可能会对他或她说，可能会对她的同事说，请让我了解情况。
That means give me updates let me know what's going on.
这意味着给我更新让我知道发生了什么。
So maybe once a week there is an alignment meeting an alignment meeting in which everybody just talks
所以也许每周有一次对齐会议 对齐会议，每个人都只是在讨论
about what's going on so that nobody is out of alignment.
关于正在发生的事情，这样没有人会不协调。
Nobody is out of the loop which is a very common phrase as well.
没有人不在循环中，这也是一个非常常见的短语。
All right now we're going to go on and we're going to actually talk about a proposal and how we can
好的，现在我们将继续，我们将实际讨论一个提案以及我们如何能够
make a proposal in a meeting situation.
在开会的情况下提出建议。